import styles from './Investors.module.css'

export default function Investors() {
  return (
    <section className={styles.investors} aria-label="Investor relations" id="investors">
      <div className={styles.inner}>

        <div className="eyebrow">IntexiaU Ventures</div>
        <h2>Built for Those Who See What's Coming</h2>
        <p className={styles.lead}>
          The AI economy is not a future event — it is happening now. IntexiaU Corp is building the{' '}
          <em>infrastructure layer</em> for how universities, medical organizations, media companies,
          and entrepreneurs will operate inside it. If you are looking for where to enter, we would
          love to have that conversation.
        </p>

        <div className={styles.opportunityGrid}>
          <div className={styles.oppCard}>
            <span className={styles.oppIcon}>🎓</span>
            <h4>University &amp; Education Operations</h4>
            <p>AI-native platforms purpose-built to operate accredited universities and learning institutions — from enrollment and curriculum delivery to workforce outcomes and credentialing.</p>
          </div>
          <div className={styles.oppCard}>
            <span className={styles.oppIcon}>🏥</span>
            <h4>Medical Office &amp; Healthcare</h4>
            <p>Intelligent platforms designed for medical offices and healthcare organizations — streamlining patient communication, legal information, administrative workflow, and care coordination.</p>
          </div>
          <div className={styles.oppCard}>
            <span className={styles.oppIcon}>📡</span>
            <h4>Media &amp; Publishing Organizations</h4>
            <p>AI-native media infrastructure for editorial teams, newsletters, broadcast organizations, and content channels — built around the Brvenik Brief Media model.</p>
          </div>
        </div>

        <div className={styles.statement}>
          <p>We are not here to pitch a deck. We are here to build something that lasts — and we are looking for partners who understand that the platforms shaping the AI economy are being built right now, not five years from now.</p>
          <span className={styles.attribution}>Andrea Brvenik — Founder &amp; CEO, IntexiaU Corp</span>
        </div>

        <div className={styles.contactWrap}>
          <h3>Let's Organize a Conversation</h3>
          <p className={styles.formSub}>
            No pitch decks required. No forms to fill. Just reach out directly and we will find a
            time to talk — whether you are an investor, a potential partner, or simply curious
            about what is being built.
          </p>

          <a href="mailto:investors@intexiaU.com" className="empathy-cta">
            investors@intexiaU.com
          </a>

          <p className={styles.note}>
            We review every message personally. You will hear back within 48 hours.
          </p>
        </div>

      </div>
    </section>
  )
}
